-Hey, guys. -Hey.
-嗨！ -嗨！
-Hi. -Hey.
We need to talk about something.
啊，有點事和你們談談。
Yeah. We don't feel like we can host Thanksgiving this year.
我們覺得... 今年我們不能再作東感恩節晚餐了。
-What? -Are you kidding?
-什麼，什麼？ -什麼，你是在開玩笑吧
Well, it's just with work and the stress of adoption..
嗯，由於工作，還有領養孩子的壓力
we don't feel like we have the energy.
我們只是覺得沒有精力弄了。
Plus, we don't think it's fair that every year the burden falls on us.
而且，每年都讓我們受累，不公平。
That doesn't sound like you.
這不像你啊！
That's Monica talking.
這像是莫尼卡的話！
-No, we made this decision together. -She's putting words in your mouth.
-不，不，這是我們兩個人的決定！ -這一定是她的意思！  （英文直譯：莫尼卡把話語放在了錢德勒的嘴裡）
Don't you put words in people's mouths. You put turkey in people's mouths.
你不應該把話送到我們口中 而是把火雞送到我們口中……
I can't believe this. This is Emma's first Thanksgiving.
無法相信 這可是艾瑪的第一個感恩節！
-No, it's not. -It's not? When was she born?
-不是... -不是？她什麼時候出生的？
Well, personally, I think it's great you're giving yourself a break.
我個人認為，你們是應該休息一下子了。
-Thank you, Phoebe. -Sure. It's just as well.
-謝謝，菲比。 -不客氣, 這樣倒好
I mean, last year wasn't very good. I think she's losing her touch.
還有，去年的晚餐真好啊 她已江郎才盡，今年不會更好了。
-What? You are way off, lady. -Am I? Really? Am I?
-什麼？你搞錯了，女士！ -是麼？
Well, why don't you cook Thanksgiving dinner and prove me wrong.
那你就再弄一次，證明我錯。
Well, think about it. You'd be trying to top what you did last year.
你想想 你是在試圖超過去年的頂峰
You'd be in competition with yourself.
你是在和...自己競爭！
That's my favorite kind.
真對我胃口！
Okay, we are doing this.
好吧，今年，我們繼續！
Don't let yourself get manipulated this way.
別讓自己這麼容易被左右。
Stay out of this, Chandler. This is between me and me.
不關你的事，錢德 這是我和……「我」之間的事情！
We are supposed to make these decisions together.
我們應該一起決定啊！
Did you not watch the Dr. Phil I taped for you?
還記得費勒醫生說的麼？
The One With The Late Thanksgiving
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Hey. -Hi. Happy Thanksgiving.
-嗨 -嗨，感恩節快樂！
Happy Meatless Turkey-Murder Day.
耶，火雞殉難日快樂！
You guys, I ordered some chocolate pies from that bakery on Bleeker.
我訂了些巧克力派
-Could you pick them up for me? -You're not making the pies?
-你們能幫我去取過來麼？ -你不自己作派嗎？
I don't make chocolate pies.
不，我不做巧克力派的。
When I was younger, I entered this pie-eating contest.
我小時候參加過一個吃派比賽
I ate so many that the thought of them makes me sick.
吃的太多了，導致我一想就噁心。
Did you at least win the contest?
那你贏了沒有？
Two minutes, twelve pies and a part of one tin.
兩分鐘吃了12個外加一罐！
-Okay, I'll see you guys at 4. -Can't wait.
-好吧，我們4點見。 -很讓人期待哦！
This dinner is gonna be so great. In your face, last-year me.
去年的莫妮卡, 我要你好看！
-Hey, Rach? -Yeah.
-嗨，瑞秋 -嗯？
What's Emma doing today?
艾瑪今天有事麼？
Well, let's see, I know that she has a meeting with her lawyer..
嗯，她啊，我只知道她今天要和律師見面
and then she has to make a very big poop.
然後做一個重大的決定。
-Why? -I want to enter her in a baby pageant.
-怎麼了？ -嗯，我想讓她參加嬰兒選美。
Oh, my God. That's the creepiest thing I've ever heard.
哦，天哪，這是我聽說過的最奇怪的事情。
Okay, but before you say no, my friend Suzanne is entering her kid.
我朋友蘇珊帶她的孩子參加了
And compared to Emma, she's a real dog.
和艾瑪比起來，那小傢伙就像只小狗！
-Phoebe, all babies are beautiful. -Oh, okay.
-哦，菲比，所有孩子都是美麗的！ -好吧
No. Phoebe, just the idea of pitting one baby against another..
菲比，難道我們只是為了一個獎盃
I mean, you know, and judging who's cuter just for a trophy..
就把孩子們比來比去，決定誰更漂亮麼？
-And a thousand dollars. -is something I'm very interested in.
-一千美金。 -對此我很感興趣！
Oh, please, do not tell Ross.
對了，別告訴羅斯。
He still believes that what's on the inside is important.
他始終不信任那些內部的...
Okay. And Emma needs a cowgirl outfit for the competition.
對了，艾瑪得穿牛仔裝！
Where am I gonna get a cowgirl outfit on Thanksgiving?
感恩節我上哪兒找牛仔裝啊？
Well, I was thinking..
讓我想想……
Take the clothes off Joey's Cabbage Patch Kid!
把喬伊的菜地娃的衣服扒了！
Did someone drop the baton again?
又有人把指揮棒給掉了？
Why come all the way from Kansas to do that?
為什麼每次都是堪薩斯的？
I don't get older, I just get better.
我不是越來越老，而是越來越好！
You know what just occurred to me?
你知道我剛想到什麼？
This could be our last Thanksgiving just the two of us.
這可能是最後一次 只有我們兩個人一起過感恩節了。
I mean, we could be getting a baby soon.
我覺得，我們很快就會有個孩子了！
-You don't know that. -Somebody's gonna pick us.
-你怎麼知道？ -有人會選擇我們的。
But we haven't heard a thing from the adoption agency.
可是這幾周我們都沒收到領養消息！
I'm telling you, it's gonna happen.
我敢保證
Next year, it's gonna be you, me and little Hemingway Bing.
明年會是你、我、還有海明威--賓！
-What? He's my favorite author. -Name one of his books.
-……嗯，因為他是我最喜歡的作家。 -說出他一本書的名字。
The Firm?
《企業》？
Okay, let's see. Okay, the turkey's in the oven. The stuffing is ready.
好吧，火雞已經在烤箱裡了 填料也準備好了。
You know, you always cook this meal all by yourself. Let me help this year.
你知道麼，你總是自己弄這些東西 今年讓我幫幫你吧。
Oh, Chandler, that's sweet.
哦，錢德，這太好了！
But you don't have to do everything Dr. Phil tells you to do.
但你不用一直按費爾醫生說的作
I'm serious, let me do something. Just not the turkey. Nothing high-profile.
我是認真的。讓我做點什麼吧 不是火雞，也不是填餡，做點不難的東西。 .
Okay, let's see. Oh, the cranberry sauce.
我想想……啊，酸梅醬！
It's easy to make, and no one really cares about it.
容易做，而且大家也不是很在意那東西！
Tell me more.
說來聽聽？
I'm gonna go check on something across the hall. You start by washing these.
我去對門兒檢查別的 你先把這個洗乾淨吧。
Not with soap!
別用洗滌劑！！
You obviously haven't tasted my Palmolive potatoes.
你肯定沒吃過我做的烤土豆……
-Hi. Hey, guess what Joey has. -Three tickets to today's Rangers game!
-嘿，猜猜喬伊拿到了什麼？ -三張今天紐約游騎兵的票（美國冰球大聯盟NHL）！
Dude, I wanted him to guess.
兄弟，我是讓他猜的！
-Oh, my God. -Yeah, they're great seats too.
-哦，天哪！ -是啊，而且是好座位哦！
-Guess where they are. -Center ice.
-猜猜什麼位置？ -正中間！
Did I do something to you?
我是不是和你有什麼過節？
-The game's at 1. -So?
-嗯，比賽一點開始。 -怎樣？
-Dinner's at 4. We'll never make it back. -So we'll leave before it's over.
-晚飯4點開始，我們趕不回來的。 -那我們就提前退場，這樣時間就夠了。
But it could take us a long time to get back home.
你現在這麼說，可是到時候必定 要花很多時間回來的
Plus, Joey could get lost and they could have to page us to go pick him up.
另外 喬伊可能會迷路，還得把他領回來。
Dude, two times that happened!
老兄，事不過三！
Look, Monica's been working hard all day.
莫尼卡為了做晚飯忙了一整天
She didn't want to host in the first place. We shouldn't go.
她希望她的晚餐最重要，我們不該去的。
He's right, man.
他說得沒錯兒
-Yeah, I guess. So we'll see you at 4. -Okay.
-好吧。那麼四點鐘見。 -嗯
And get ready to taste my very special cranberries.
準備好品嚐我的特製酸梅醬哦！
Or should I say "Chan-berries"?
或者，應該叫做「錢梅」...
That's some gentle comedy, dude.
夥計，又不是在演輕喜劇
-We're still going to the game, right? -Yeah.
-我們要去看比賽吧？ -是的！
This is contestant number 16, Rebecca Hope from Yonkers.
這是16號運動員 來自楊克斯的Rebecca Hope
-Hey. -Phoebe, listen, I think we gotta go.
-嘿！ -菲比，我想走了
This place is freaking me out.
這地方讓我坐立不安。
I've been watching this guy over there. I don't think he came with a kid.
你看到那邊那個人了麼 我可不認為他帶來的是個孩子！
But we can't leave now.
但我們現在不能離開啊
There was this one baby, Haley, who was favored to win..
最被看好的那個孩子Haley
she got croup, so she had to stay home.
因為感冒不能來
This competition just blew wide-open, folks.
競爭才剛剛開始哦！
Phoebe, it's just too weird.
菲比，這太奇怪了
I just saw a 1-year-old with pantyhose on.
我看見一個一歲的小孩穿連褲襪！
Oh, I know. We should've been more prepared.
哦，我就覺得我們準備不夠充分
It's okay. Now, the way I see it, our real competition now is Cameron.
我覺得，咱們最有力的競爭對手是卡米隆。
My God, they just took her sweater off.
哦，天哪，她的衣服被脫掉了
Look at those arms. Hello, Michelin Man.
看她的手臂，就像...米其林 （著名輪胎的卡通形象，綠色滴~~）
Phoebe, come on. You know what, it's already 3:00.
菲比，已經三點鐘了 而他們還沒有評審到艾瑪這一組
They haven't even gotten to Emma's group yet. We got dinner.
我們該走了，回去吃飯。
But Emma's got what it takes. She could go all the way!
但艾瑪今天肯定能贏
-Phoebe, you have to calm down. -Okay.
-菲比，冷靜點。 -好吧，
Rachel, the hottest babies in the tri-state area are in this room right now.
瑞秋，現在 這附近最漂亮的寶貝們都在這裡了。
I overheard a judge say that not one of them holds a candle to Emma.
而我聽見一個評審說 沒人比得過艾瑪。
-Really? -Yeah.
-真的麼？ -沒錯！
-You heard him say that? -Yeah.
-你聽見他們這麼說？ -對。
All right. Okay. All right, let's give these babies something to cry about.
好吧，那就讓我們 給其他的孩子們一點悲慘的回憶！
Good. Let's get down to business. Emma needs some makeup.
太好了，開工吧！艾瑪需要化妝。
What?
什麼？
She's gonna look washed-out next to the others.
她應該比其他孩子看起來更漂亮！
No, I'm not letting you put makeup on my baby.
菲比，我不會讓你給我的孩子化妝的！
-Why not? -Because I already did.
-為什麼不？ -因為我已經給她化過了！
You suck! Get off the ice, you idiot!
鮑伯，幹掉那傢伙！
-What a game. -I know. Yeah.
-太精彩了！ -沒錯，耶！
-I can't believe Chandler's missing this. -I'm sorry he's not here.
-真遺憾錢德錯過了這場比賽！ -我也替他覺得遺憾
But I gotta say, I am really enjoying nacho chair.
但我要說的是，我真的很喜歡這個「玉米片」座！
Yeah, I'd probably enjoy it more if you didn't keep batting my hand away.
嗯，要是你不總是把我的手打開， 我可能也會吃不少呢
-Yeah! -These seats are great.
-哦！ -這位置太棒了！
I know, I know. When I was here for "Holidays on lce"..
是啊，沒錯！ 上次假期我在這看比賽，座位太遠了
I was sitting so far away, Michelle Kwan couldn't read my banner.
關穎珊（花樣滑冰世界冠軍）根本就看不到我舉的條幅。
Dude, I'm sure she knows you heart her.
老兄, 我認為她知道你心裡有她
I hope so.
希望吧
We'd better get going. If we don't leave now, we're gonna be late.
嘿，我們該走了啦，回去吃飯。
But it's a tie game. So we're a little late. The girls will be there.
可比賽太精彩了！ 我們可以晚回去點吧，女生們應該準時的
Let's just stay for one more goal.
再進一個球再走啦
-I don't know. -One more fight.
-不好吧.. -再進攻一輪？
-Okay. -Okay.
-好吧。 -好吧。
Where is everybody? They're 45 minutes late.
大家都哪裡去了？他們遲到了45分鐘！
I can't believe they're not here. I slave and I slave for what?
我不相信他們會不來！我辛苦了一天 而我這麼辛苦是為了什麼？
They've ruined Cranberry Day.
他們毀了我的酸梅日！
-How late are we? -Forty-five minutes.
-我們遲到了多久？ -45分鐘
-Here. -Okay.
-給. -好的.
Rachel and Phoebe are already there, so they probably started without us.
瑞秋和菲比應該已經到了 也就是說她們應該已經開始了
We could just slip in, and no one needs to know where we were.
讓我們溜進去，這樣誰都不會注意我們的。
-You may want to lose the foam finger. -Oh, no, no, no.
-你不把這個泡沫大手指扔掉麼？ -哦，才不呢！
You just want to put it on your hand.
我知道你想搶走他！
-You're not at Thanksgiving? -No, we're late.
-你們沒在裡面？ -不，我們遲到了！
-What are you doing here? -We're late too.
-你們在這裡幹什麼？ -我們也遲到了！
We figured we could be late because you'd be on time.
我們本以為你們不會遲到的！
Don't point that thing at me, Tribbiani.
別用這個指著我，崔比阿尼！
-Nobody's here? Monica's gonna kill us. -Yeah, where were you?
-那...裡面沒人，莫尼卡會殺了我們的！ -你們到什麼地方去了？
-Well.. -Yeah, what's with the trophy?
-啊… -那是什麼獎盃？
Well, we were at a spelling bee.
嗯，我們去參加拼字大賽了。
And I won.
我贏了！
You won an adult Thanksgiving Day spelling bee?
你在感恩節這天 贏得了一場成人拼字遊戲？
Yes. Y-E-S. Yes.
是-的, 是的！
Let me see this. "Grand Supreme Little Darling, New York Division"?
讓我看看…… 超級小可愛，紐約區。
That's me.
那便是我！
You entered Emma in a beauty pageant?
你們讓艾瑪參加了選美比賽？
And it looks like she put makeup on her.
而且還給她化了妝！
Wait a second. Where have I seen that cowgirl outfit before?
等等，等等 我好像在什麼地方見過這身牛仔...
I can't believe this. She's our daughter.
無法置信，她是我們的女兒！
That you would treat her like some kind of show dog is inexcusable.
你把她當成觀賞狗一樣，不可饒恕
-She won a thousand dollars. -So this is an annual thing?
-她為我們贏得了一千美元！ -啊，是一年一次的嗎……
That's Alicia May Emory's outfit!
啊，這是Alicia Mae的裝備！
Guys, there are people in there who are not getting any happier.
夥計們，有人在裡面要發火了！
-What are we gonna do? -I gotta put Emma down for a nap.
-天哪，我們該怎麼辦？ -我不知道，你們想吧, 我先把艾瑪送回去。
And, Rach, while you're in there, throw something on Alicia May.
哦，瑞秋，至少給個主意嗎
-All right, what are we gonna say? -We'll say that we were mugged.
-我們該怎麼說？ -我們可以說，我們被搶劫了
You can't get mad at someone who's been mugged.
當有人被搶了的時候，是不能生氣的！
Good. But you don't look like you were mugged.
嗯，不錯，但你看起來不像被搶過。
No. Here.
不像..這樣才像
Hey!
嘿！
Do you hear something?
你有沒有聽到什麼？
-They're out there. -Let me see.
-他們都在外面！ -讓我看看！
I can't believe this. They're an hour late, and they're just standing there talking.
我真沒辦法相信，他們遲到了一小時 還在那裡聊天！
Everything's so distorted. It looks like Joey has a giant hand.
一切都亂套了，喬伊有只大手！
That says "Rangers" on it. They went to the game.
上面寫「游騎兵」，他們去看比賽了！
Oh, they are in for a world of pain.
哦，這太可怕了！
-Ross' shirt is torn. -They're late and they're sloppy.
-羅斯的襯衫撕壞了。 -他們不但遲到，而且衣衫不整！
All right, Emma's napping. What happened to your shirt?
好了，艾瑪睡下了。你的襯衫怎麼了？
I got mugged, and they stole my pocket.
我被搶了，他們還偷走了我的錢包。
We're just trying to figure out an excuse.
瑞秋，我們是在找借口。
How about this?
好吧，想想
We could say that Monica told us 5:00, not 4:00. That way we're right on time.
我們可以說，莫尼卡告訴我們是5點 而不是4點，所以我們沒遲到，我們是準時的！
Or we could plant PCP in the apartment and call the cops on her.
或者, 我們可以在房間裡放些迷藥，佈個局！
That would be a good way to get rid of all the PCP we have lying around.
嗯，這的確是個下迷藥的好辦法。
We'll just say that she said it was 5:00.
你可以就說她說的是5點
We'll just act casual. We're not late, we're right on time.
做得自然些 所以我們根本沒有遲到！
"We know you're out there."
「我們知道你們在外面。」
Who do you think it's from?
你覺得這是誰寫的？
Oh, God, this is bad. This is so bad.
哦，太糟了，太糟了。
Well, let's just go in there and face them.
好吧，讓我們進去面對他們吧。
I'm not going in first. I bet that vein on Monica's forehead is popping like crazy.
我不要先進去 莫尼卡生氣的面孔會讓我發瘋的。
I hate that thing. It's like a bolt of lightning.
嗯，我也不要 那張臉就像扭曲的閃電一樣……
Why don't we play Rock, Paper, Scissors, and whoever loses, goes in first.
嘿，我有主意了 我們可以玩石頭剪子布，輸了的先進去！
-All right, I'm in. -Ready.
-好吧，開始吧。 -準備好了麼？
I win.
啊，我贏了！
-What is that? -That's fire. It beats everything.
-這是什麼？ -火焰，贏過一切！
Oh, really? Does it beat water balloon?
真的麼？能贏過一個水球麼？
Well-played, Phoebe Buffay. Well-played.
好極了，菲比，玩得真好。
All right, let's all go in at the same time.
好啦好啦，讓我們一起進去算了。
-Okay. -Okay.
-好。 -好。
-It's locked. -What? Oh, sure, now they lock it.
-鎖住了！ -哈，他們把門鎖上了
When they're having sex on the couch, it's like:
等他們在躺椅上 準備嘿咻的時候，他們就會說
"Come on in, my butt is surprisingly hairy!"
「啊，快進來，快進來，我等不了了！」
All right, come on. All right, you guys, we're so sorry we're late.
好吧。夥計們，你們怎麼樣啊？ 很抱歉我們遲到了
Please let us in so we can have dinner together.
讓我們進去一起吃晚餐吧！
No, everything's cold. The turkey's dried out and the stuffing's all soggy.
不，東西都涼了 火雞干了，餡也鬆了！
Yeah, and there's a bowl of cranberry sauce that's..
嗯，而且那碗酸梅醬也……
What happens to cranberry sauce?
酸梅醬怎麼了？
-Nothing, it's fine. -Oh, thank God.
-沒事兒，很好。 -哦，謝天謝地。
Come on, you guys, we're sorry. Our subway broke down.
好啦，夥計們 真的抱歉，我們的車壞了。
That's a lie! You went to the game. I can see Joey's hand.
說謊！你們去看比賽了 我能看到喬伊的手！
For the love of God, take it off!
我說過了讓你把它扔掉了！
Guys, it doesn't matter why we're late. We're all here now.
夥計們，我們是否遲到了並不重要 重要的是我們都到了
Please let us in so we can have some of your delicious turkey.
讓我們進去吃美味的火雞吧！
I had a dream once about a fax machine that did that.
我做夢都在想啊，這是什麼？
That's all the turkey you're gonna get.
這就是你們該得的火雞！
-How are we gonna decide who gets this? -Water balloon!
-怎麼決定誰吃？ -水球！
What are we gonna do? I'm starving.
我們該怎麼辦啊，我餓死了！
I just remembered, we do have something to eat.
哦，對了，我想起來了
Monica put something in our oven this morning.
今天早晨莫尼卡放了點東西在爐子裡面！
You touch that, and you will be sorry!
嘿，動了它你會後悔的！
Guys, I'd listen to her. The vein is bigger than I've ever seen it!
大伙, 最好聽她的 她的血管漲到前所未有的大
Oh, my God, it's Brussels sprouts!
天哪，是甘藍菜！
That's worse than no food.
這是什麼嘛，不能吃的！
All you got was Monica's stinky Brussels sprouts.
啊哈，你們喜歡莫尼卡的發臭的甘藍菜麼？
Stinky?
發臭的？
Please let me stay on this side of the door.
請讓我呆在這一邊……
Oh, I know! I still have my old key.
對了，我還有以前的鑰匙呢。
We can just unlock the door.
我們可以直接把門打開！
I don't know if that's a good idea. They don't wanna be with us.
我不覺得這是個好主意 他們明顯不想和我們在一起。
I don't wanna be with them either..
你知道麼，我也不想和他們一起
but it's Thanksgiving, and we should not want to be together together.
但今天是感恩節，不想在一起也要在一起！
If I could just get in there, make a face-to-face apology..
讓我們進去面對面的道歉吧
look them in the eye, I could get them to forgive us.
看到我的眼睛，他們就會原諒我的。
-I don't know. -I'm telling you..
-我不懂。 -我來告訴你……
I can do it.
我做得到。
Yeah, he can do it.
嗯，你做得到。
It all looks so beautiful.
啊，太美了！
-The turkey, the stuffing. -The cranberries.
-那火雞，那填料…… -那酸梅呢？
Enough! A monkey could've made them.
夠了，猴子都會做！
Hey, listen, guys, we feel really terrible.
嘿，聽我說，我們真得很抱歉……
He's doing that weird eye-contact thing.
他又來那什麼「目光接觸」了
Don't look at him. Don't look at him.
別看他，別看他。
Come on, you guys. We want you to know we're very, very sorry.
聽我說，夥計們，我們想讓你們瞭解 我們真的，真的很抱歉……
Right, guys?
對吧，夥計們？
-I feel terrible. -Oh, so sorry.
-真的很抱歉 -非常，對不起……
But let's not ruin this day. You've worked so hard.
別讓我們毀了這一天，你們如此的辛勞！
Let's move past this and try to have a nice meal all together, huh?
讓我們忘了這件事，一起吃飯吧！
The floating heads do make a good point.
那些漂浮著的腦袋好像說的沒錯。
Yeah, they do seem to feel pretty bad.
是啊，他們真的好像很抱歉。
-So bad. -So bad.
-對不起，對不起…… -對不起，對不起……
Okay.
好吧
Okay, you two go get the dessert, and I'll let you in.
好吧，你們兩個去拿甜品來 我讓你們進來。
Dessert?
甜品？
Yeah, I asked you and Phoebe to pick up the pies. You did remember, right?
是啊，我讓你和菲比去取派 你記得的，對吧？
Pies. Oh, we thought you said "prize."
派？啊，我們以為是「獎」！ (註：英語中「派」和「獎」發音相同。）
Here.
這個！
-"Grand Supreme Little Darling"? -Congratulations!
-超級小可愛？ -恭喜！
Oh, my God, you forgot the pies? Well, I cannot believe this.
天哪，你忘了拿派？無法置信！
You forced me to make dinner, you're an hour late..
你們強迫我做飯，又遲到一小時
and you forget the one little thing that I asked you to do.
居然還忘記了我拜託你們做的一點點小事！
Really, girls, not cool.
真的，女孩子們真冷酷。
Well, you man-heads aren't any better. You lied about going to the game.
好吧，你們男人又好到哪裡去？ 你們說謊，去看比賽
You knew it'd make you late, and you went anyway.
明知道會遲到，還堅持要去。
Hey, I'm getting a little tired of this. We said we're sorry.
我有點煩了。我們都道歉了
It's Thanksgiving, for Pete's sakes! A day of forgiveness.
今天是感恩節，是原諒之日！
-It's a day to be thankful. -Don't make me come up there!
-是感謝之日吧…… -別和我唱反調！
It's too late for apologies.
現在道歉太晚了！
Fine, let's just go. I don't need your stupid dinner.
好吧，我們走，我們可以不在這裡吃飯！
That would be a lot more convincing if you weren't drooling.
如果你們開玩笑的話，可能更可信點。
-Oh, is that what that is? -Sorry.
-哦，我們現在就不是麼？ -對不起
Come on, you guys, let's just do our own Thanksgiving.
夥計們，我們自己準備感恩節晚餐吧！
-Yeah, I'll cook. -Yeah, let's go out.
-好，我做飯！ -好，走吧！
Yeah, you three have a nice Thanksgiving.
你們三個，感恩節快樂！
-The three of us? -Yeah. You, Chan and the vein.
-三個？ -你，錢德，還有「白忙活」！
-I'm stuck. -Joey, that is not gonna work.
-啊，我被卡住了！ -喬伊，少來！
No, seriously.
不，我是認真的
-I'm really wedged in here. -I'll pull you through.
-我真的被卡住了 -我把你拖過來
Okay.
好。
Stop, stop, I'm worried about damaging my head.
啊，住手，住手 我擔心會弄傷我的頭！
It's a little late for that.
已經晚了
Hurry up, you gotta do something.
快點，幫幫忙啊！
All right, well, this does not change anything.
這不會改變什麼的！
We need to get something to grease his face.
我們需要點能增大空隙的工具。
-We got turkey grease. -Bring it.
-我們有火雞汁！ -拿來。
I just want to say that I'm sorry I referred to the vein as a separate person.
我很抱歉，我把「白忙活」算作一個人
Here you go.
拿來了。
Oh, that smells good.
啊，味道不錯
-Okay? -Okay, try it.
-好了嗎？ -好，試試看。
It isn't working.
沒用！
-We're gonna have to unscrew the chain. -Hurry, I can't feel my ears.
-把鏈條卸下來吧。 -快點，我都感覺不到我的耳朵了！
Can you ever feel your ears?
你曾經感覺到過耳朵麼？
Interesting.
嗯，很有趣。
-Chandler, where are your tools? -Oh, I left them on my bulldozer.
-錢德，你的工具哪裡去了？ -啊，我把它們放在別的地方了。
I don't have tools.
我沒有工具。
-Well, I do, but Rachel borrowed them. -I lent them to Ross.
-我有，但被瑞秋借去了。 -我借給了羅斯。
-I gave them to Joey. -I left them at the park.
-我給了喬伊。 -我留在車庫了。
I'm finding it really hard not to mess with him.
這還真麻煩。
I stuffed Brussels sprouts down his pants.
我早就已經被他褲子裡的甘藍菜味道弄暈了。
Nice.
很好。
Okay, I have to get that.
好，我去接電話
Now, when I get back, I want you and your friends to be gone.
當我回來的時候 我希望你和你的朋友們已經離開了。
Thanksgiving is over. The vein has spoken.
感恩節完了！這是「白忙活」說的！
-It's really starting to hurt. -Look, I'm gonna pull on the door..
-我的頭真的被卡住了！ -好吧，我會拉門
and you guys push. Maybe we can get enough room to wiggle him out, okay?
然後你們努力推 這樣他就有足夠的空隙出來了，好吧？
Okay, so push.
好，推吧！
Just a sec. We're kind of in the middle of something here.
啊，等下，我們正忙著……
Hey, stop putting things down my pants.
別往我的褲子裡面放東西！
-Come on, guys, push! -Yeah, come on, push!
-來吧，夥計們，推吧！ -來，推，推，推！
Push! Push!
推，推！
-My cranberries! -Man, I got food all over me.
-我的酸梅！ -我全身都是！
I can't believe what you did. Monica's gonna kill you.
慘不忍睹，莫尼卡會殺了你的！
Look! Look! Look what the.. Look what the floating heads did!
看，看，看 這個「漂腦袋」作了什麼？
I don't care.
沒關係。
What's going on?
怎麼了？
That was the adoption agency.
是領養管理處打來的。
And?
然後？
-We're getting a baby! -Are you serious?!
-我們可以領養孩子了！ -真的麼？
There's a pregnant woman in Ohio, and she picked us.
有個俄亥俄州的孕婦選了我們！
-Oh, my God, that's great! -That's incredible.
-恭喜！真為你們高興！ -太好了！
I'm so happy for you.
恭喜你們！
This Thanksgiving kicks last Thanksgiving's ass!
今年的感恩節比去年好太多了！
To Monica and Chandler and that knocked-up girl in Ohio.
敬莫尼卡和錢德 還有那俄亥俄州的小傢伙！
I'm just so happy you guys are finally getting a kid.
你們兩個終於有孩子了，這真讓我高興。
I know. Have you considered pageanting?
你們沒考慮過懷孕麼？
I can't believe they called. I mean, we're actually getting a baby.
他們打來電話，我們就會有孩子了 這真是不可思議！
I know how you feel.
我能體會你們的感受。
-Really? -Sure.
-真的麼？ -當然啦
I went through the exact same thing with Alicia May Emory.
我以前經歷過完全相同的事情。
The waiting, the wondering.
那種期待，那種迷茫
Then one day, I get that call from Toys "R" Us.
直到有一天 我從托伊那家店買到了那車！
She was in stock.
她又有貨了！
That is the exact same thing.
確實「完全相同」。